(this.webpackJsonpmilionaire=this.webpackJsonpmilionaire||[]).push([[0],{10:function(t,e,r){},12:function(t,e,r){"use strict";r.r(e);var o=r(1),c=r.n(o),s=r(5),i=r.n(s),a=r(2),n=(r(10),r(0));function h(t){var e=t.setUsername,r=Object(o.useRef)();return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"start",children:[Object(n.jsx)("input",{className:"startInput",placeholder:"enter your name",ref:r}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(t){r.current.value&&e(r.current.value)},children:"Start"})]})}function u(t){var e=t.setTimeOut,r=t.questionNumber,c=Object(o.useState)(30),s=Object(a.a)(c,2),i=s[0],n=s[1];return Object(o.useEffect)((function(){if(0===i)return e(!0);var t=setInterval((function(){n((function(t){return t-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(t)}}),[i,e]),Object(o.useEffect)((function(){n(30)}),[r]),i}var d=r(3),m=r.p+"static/media/play.8e5f6d1d.mp3",l=r.p+"static/media/correct.160572d7.mp3",x=r.p+"static/media/wrong.e9468218.mp3";function b(t){var e=t.data,r=t.questionNumber,c=t.setQuestionNumber,s=t.setTimeOut,i=Object(o.useState)(null),h=Object(a.a)(i,2),u=h[0],b=h[1],w=Object(o.useState)(null),f=Object(a.a)(w,2),j=f[0],p=f[1],$=Object(o.useState)("answer"),O=Object(a.a)($,2),y=O[0],v=O[1],g=Object(d.a)(m),A=Object(a.a)(g,1)[0],q=Object(d.a)(l),B=Object(a.a)(q,1)[0],C=Object(d.a)(x),D=Object(a.a)(C,1)[0];Object(o.useEffect)((function(){A()}),[A]),Object(o.useEffect)((function(){b(e[r-1])}),[e,r]);var J=function(t,e){setTimeout((function(){e()}),t)};return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"trivia",children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:null===u||void 0===u?void 0:u.question}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:null===u||void 0===u?void 0:u.answers.map((function(t){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:j===t?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return!j&&function(t){p(t),v("answer active"),J(3e3,(function(){v(t.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")})),J(5e3,(function(){t.correct?(B(),J(1e3,(function(){c((function(t){return t+1})),p(null)}))):(D(),J(1e3,(function(){s(!0)})))}))}(t)},children:t.text})}))})]})}var w=function(){var t=Object(o.useState)(null),e=Object(a.a)(t,2),r=e[0],c=e[1],s=Object(o.useState)(!1),i=Object(a.a)(s,2),d=i[0],m=i[1],l=Object(o.useState)(1),x=Object(a.a)(l,2),w=x[0],f=x[1],j=Object(o.useState)("$ 0"),p=Object(a.a)(j,2),$=p[0],O=p[1],y=Object(o.useMemo)((function(){return[{id:1,amount:"$ 10"},{id:2,amount:"$ 20"},{id:3,amount:"$ 30"},{id:4,amount:"$ 40"},{id:5,amount:"$ 50"},{id:6,amount:"$ 60"},{id:7,amount:"$ 70"},{id:8,amount:"$ 80"},{id:9,amount:"$ 90"},{id:10,amount:"$ 100"},{id:11,amount:"$ 200"},{id:12,amount:"$ 300"},{id:13,amount:"$ 400"},{id:14,amount:"$ 500"},{id:15,amount:"$ 1000"},{id:16,amount:"$ 2000"},{id:17,amount:"$ 3.000"},{id:18,amount:"$ 4000"},{id:19,amount:"$ 5.000"},{id:20,amount:"$ 6.000"},{id:21,amount:"$ 7.000"},{id:22,amount:"$ 8.000"},{id:23,amount:"$ 9.000"},{id:24,amount:"$ 10.000"},{id:25,amount:"$ 20.000"},{id:26,amount:"$ 30.000"},{id:27,amount:"$ 40.000"},{id:28,amount:"$ 50.000"},{id:29,amount:"$ 60.000"},{id:30,amount:"$ 70.000"},{id:31,amount:"$ 80.000"},{id:32,amount:"$ 90.000"},{id:33,amount:"$ 100.000"},{id:34,amount:"$ 200.000"},{id:35,amount:"$ 300.000"},{id:36,amount:"$ 400.000"},{id:37,amount:"$ 500.000"},{id:38,amount:"$ 600.000"},{id:39,amount:"$ 700.000"},{id:40,amount:"$ 800.000"},{id:41,amount:"$ 900.000"},{id:42,amount:"$ 1.000.000"},{id:43,amount:"$ 2.000.000"},{id:44,amount:"$ 3.000.000"},{id:45,amount:"$ 4.000.000"},{id:46,amount:"$ 5.000.000"},{id:47,amount:"$ 6.000.000"},{id:48,amount:"$ 7.000.000"},{id:49,amount:"$ 8.000.000"},{id:50,amount:"$ 9.000.000"},{id:51,amount:"$ 10.000.000"},{id:52,amount:"$ 20.000.000"},{id:53,amount:"$ 30.000.000"},{id:54,amount:"$ 40.000.000"},{id:55,amount:"$ 50.000.000"},{id:56,amount:"$ 60.000.000"},{id:57,amount:"$ 70.000.000"},{id:58,amount:"$ 80.000.000"},{id:59,amount:"$ 90.000.000"},{id:60,amount:"$ 100.000.000"},{id:61,amount:"$ 200.000.000"},{id:62,amount:"$ 300.000.000"},{id:63,amount:"$ 400.000.000"},{id:64,amount:"$ 500.000.000"},{id:65,amount:"$ 600.000.000"},{id:66,amount:"$ 700.000.000"},{id:67,amount:"$ 800.000.000"},{id:68,amount:"$ 900.000.000"},{id:69,amount:"$ 1.000.000.000"},{id:70,amount:"$ 2.000.000.000"},{id:71,amount:"$ 3.000.000.000"},{id:72,amount:"$ 4.000.000.000"},{id:73,amount:"$ 5.000.000.000"},{id:74,amount:"$ 6.000.000.000"},{id:75,amount:"$ 7.000.000.000"}]}),[]);return Object(o.useEffect)((function(){w>1&&O(y.find((function(t){return t.id===w-1})).amount)}),[w,y]),Object(n.jsx)(n.Fragment,{children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:r?Object(n.jsxs)(n.Fragment,{children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"main",children:d?Object(n.jsxs)(n.Fragment,{children:[Object(n.jsxs)("h1",{className:"activeText",children:["Congratulations ",r,", You earned: ",$]}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"restartButton",onClick:function(){window.location.reload()},children:"RESTART"})]}):Object(n.jsxs)(n.Fragment,{children:[Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"top",children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(n.jsx)(u,{setTimeOut:m,questionNumber:w})}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:Object(n.jsxs)("h1",{className:"endText",children:[" Contestant ",r," "]})})]}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(n.jsx)(b,{data:[{id:1,question:"List these famous women in the order in which they appear in the bible. A.Mary Magdalene B. Eve C.Sarah D.Mary, the mother of God",answers:[{text:"A,B,C,D",correct:!1},{text:"B,C,D,A",correct:!0},{text:"B,C,D,C",correct:!1},{text:"B,D,C,A",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"Who visited Mary with the news that she would bear Gods's son, Jesus?",answers:[{text:"the angel Gabriel",correct:!0},{text:"the Avon Lady",correct:!1},{text:"a census taker",correct:!1},{text:"the angel Raphael",correct:!1}]},{id:3,question:"Put the following books in the order they apear in the bible.   A.REVELATION B.LUKE C.FIRST THESSELONIANS D.MATTHEW?",answers:[{text:"B,C,D,A",correct:!1},{text:"D,C,B,A",correct:!1},{text:"C,B,D,A",correct:!1},{text:"D,B,C,A",correct:!0}]},{id:4,question:"What did Delilah do to Samson to take away his strength?",answers:[{text:"talked him into fighting an army",correct:!1},{text:"blinded him",correct:!1},{text:"made him fall asleep",correct:!1},{text:"cut his hair",correct:!0}]},{id:5,question:"This was the last Gospel to be written?",answers:[{text:"Matthew",correct:!1},{text:"Luke",correct:!1},{text:"Mark",correct:!1},{text:"John",correct:!0}]},{id:6,question:"The word Sabbath means?",answers:[{text:"peace be unto you",correct:!1},{text:"Holy One",correct:!1},{text:"a day of rest",correct:!1},{text:"what's up",correct:!0}]},{id:7,question:"This twin was later renamed Israel?",answers:[{text:"Esau",correct:!1},{text:"Cain",correct:!1},{text:"Abel",correct:!1},{text:"Jacob",correct:!0}]},{id:8,question:"The official Roman charge against Jesus was that he had?",answers:[{text:"committed blasphemy",correct:!1},{text:"claimed to be a King",correct:!1},{text:"incited a revolt among the Jews",correct:!0},{text:"opposed payment of taxes to the Temple",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"This was the first Gospel to be written?",answers:[{text:"Mark",correct:!0},{text:"Luke",correct:!1},{text:"John",correct:!1},{text:"Matthew",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"What city was considered to be King David's place of origin?",answers:[{text:"Jerusalem",correct:!1},{text:"Hebron",correct:!1},{text:"Nazareth",correct:!1},{text:"Bethlehem",correct:!0}]},{id:11,question:"What is the name of Moses' sister?",answers:[{text:"Deborah",correct:!1},{text:"Zipporah",correct:!1},{text:"Miriam",correct:!0},{text:"Leah",correct:!1}]},{id:12,question:"The Gospels tells the story of what?",answers:[{text:"How a man lived",correct:!1},{text:"The Jews",correct:!1},{text:"why the chickens crossed the road",correct:!1},{text:"the life, death, and Resurrection of Jesus",correct:!0}]},{id:13,question:"Jesus used these kinds of stories to helppeople understand what the reign of God was like?",answers:[{text:"bedtime stories",correct:!1},{text:"parables",correct:!0},{text:"skits",correct:!1},{text:"dramas",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"Which King was responsible for building the Jerusalem Temple?",answers:[{text:"Saul",correct:!1},{text:"David",correct:!1},{text:"Rehoboam",correct:!1},{text:"Solomon",correct:!0}]},{id:15,question:"The term Passover is rooted in which event?",answers:[{text:"the last supper",correct:!1},{text:"the final plague",correct:!0},{text:"the Babylonian Exile",correct:!1},{text:"the Transfiguration",correct:!1}]},{id:16,question:"Place these commandments in the order in which they appear in the Bible. A. Honour your father and mother B. Remember the Sabbath Day keep it holy C. You shall not steal D. Do not covet your neighbors wife. ",answers:[{text:"B,C,A,D",correct:!1},{text:"C,B,D,A",correct:!1},{text:"A,B,C,D",correct:!1},{text:"B,A,C,D",correct:!0}]},{id:17,question:"Who led the Israelites into the promised Land of Canaan?",answers:[{text:"Jacob",correct:!1},{text:"Aaron",correct:!1},{text:"Moses",correct:!1},{text:"Joshua",correct:!0}]},{id:18,question:"List these characters in the order in which they encounter Jesus in the Gospels. A. Pilate B. Peter C. John the Baptist D. Joseph, husband of Mary",answers:[{text:"D,B,C,A",correct:!0},{text:"B,D,C,A",correct:!1},{text:"D,C,B,A",correct:!1},{text:" B,D,A,C",correct:!0}]},{id:19,question:"Who led the Israelites from slavery in Egypt across the Red Sea and to the promised Land?",answers:[{text:"King David",correct:!1},{text:"Noah, in his Ark",correct:!1},{text:"Moses",correct:!0},{text:"Galileo Galilay",correct:!0}]},{id:20,question:"Which of these foods did the Israelites depend on as they journeyed in the wilderness with Moses?",answers:[{text:"Big Macs",correct:!1},{text:"Manna",correct:!0},{text:"meatballs",correct:!1},{text:"turkey",correct:!1}]},{id:21,question:"Which of these books is not one of the prophetic books of the Old Testament?",answers:[{text:"Jeremiah",correct:!1},{text:"Leviticus",correct:!0},{text:"Isaiah",correct:!1},{text:"Daniel",correct:!1}]},{id:22,question:"The sermon on the Mount, in which Jesus teaches the beatitudes can be found in which Gospel?",answers:[{text:"Matthew",correct:!0},{text:"Luke",correct:!1},{text:"Mark",correct:!1},{text:"John",correct:!0}]},{id:23,question:"Pentecost commemorates what event for the Jews?",answers:[{text:"the Exodus from Egypt",correct:!1},{text:"the giving of the law to Moses",correct:!0},{text:"the fall of Jericho",correct:!1},{text:"the Holy Spirit inspiring the Apostles",correct:!1}]},{id:24,question:"List these famous leaders in the order in which they appear in the Old Testament. A. Jacob B. Abraham C. Moses D. Issac",answers:[{text:" B,C,D,A",correct:!1},{text:"B,C,A,D",correct:!1},{text:"B,A,C,D",correct:!1},{text:"B,D,A,C",correct:!0}]},{id:25,question:"Who is creditd with writing the Psalms?",answers:[{text:"King David",correct:!0},{text:"King Solomon",correct:!1},{text:"the grateful Dead",correct:!1},{text:"the Rolling Stones",correct:!1}]},{id:26,question:"Who wrote the Letter to the Romans?",answers:[{text:"Peter",correct:!1},{text:"Mary",correct:!1},{text:"John",correct:!1},{text:"Paul",correct:!0}]},{id:27,question:"In which Gospel does Jesus wash the feet of the disciples?",answers:[{text:"Matthew",correct:!1},{text:"Mark",correct:!1},{text:"Luke",correct:!1},{text:"John",correct:!0}]},{id:28,question:"The Acts of the Apostles was written by ?",answers:[{text:"John",correct:!1},{text:"Peter",correct:!1},{text:"Luke",correct:!0},{text:"Matthew",correct:!1}]},{id:29,question:"Who claimed Jesus' body after the Crucifixion?",answers:[{text:"Mary Magdalene",correct:!1},{text:"Nicodemus",correct:!1},{text:"John the beloved",correct:!1},{text:"Joseph of Arimathea",correct:!0}]},{id:30,question:"To test Abrahams faith, God instructed him to sacrifice his only what?",answers:[{text:"son, Issac",correct:!0},{text:"walking stick",correct:!1},{text:"chicken",correct:!1},{text:"pillow",correct:!1}]},{id:31,question:"List these major sections of the Bible in the order in which they appear. A. the historical books B. the Gospels C. the Pentatuch D. the epistles?",answers:[{text:"A,C,B,A",correct:!1},{text:"A,B,C,D",correct:!1},{text:"D,C,B,A",correct:!1},{text:"C,A,B,D",correct:!0}]},{id:32,question:"The Ark of the convenant contained what?",answers:[{text:"the Ten Commandments",correct:!0},{text:"used oil lamps",correct:!1},{text:"the remains of Moses",correct:!1},{text:"Noah's ark",correct:!1}]},{id:33,question:"Who is the most important and powerful person in the Jewish community during the time of Jesus?",answers:[{text:"Pharises",correct:!1},{text:"tax collector",correct:!1},{text:"scribe",correct:!1},{text:"high priest",correct:!0}]},{id:34,question:"Who created the golden calf for the Israelites while Moses was on Mount Sinai?",answers:[{text:"Aaron",correct:!0},{text:"Ahab",correct:!1},{text:"Joshua",correct:!1},{text:"Miriam",correct:!1}]},{id:35,question:"Who was the emoeror of Rome during the time of Jesus' birth?",answers:[{text:"Nero",correct:!1},{text:"Herod",correct:!1},{text:"Augustus",correct:!1},{text:"Pontius Pilate",correct:!1}]},{id:36,question:"Who was the mother of John the Baptist?",answers:[{text:"Maude",correct:!1},{text:"Miriam",correct:!1},{text:"Thelma",correct:!1},{text:"Elizabeth",correct:!0}]},{id:37,question:"What is the correct ending to the verse 'Blessed are the poor in spirit...'?",answers:[{text:"for they will receive an allowance",correct:!1},{text:"for they should get a job",correct:!1},{text:"for theirs is the kingdom of heaven",correct:!0},{text:"for they shall see God",correct:!1}]},{id:38,question:"After spending forty days in the wilderness, from what prophetic scroll did Jesus read while he was in the synagogue in Nazareth?",answers:[{text:"Jeremiah",correct:!1},{text:"Ezekiel",correct:!1},{text:"Daniel",correct:!1},{text:"Isaiah",correct:!0}]}],questionNumber:w,setQuestionNumber:f,setTimeOut:m})})]})}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"pyramid",children:Object(n.jsx)("ul",{className:"moneyList",children:y.map((function(t){return Object(n.jsxs)("li",{className:w===t.id?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem",children:[Object(n.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemNumber",children:t.id}),Object(n.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemAmount",children:t.amount})]})}))})})]}):Object(n.jsx)(h,{setUsername:c})})})};i.a.render(Object(n.jsx)(c.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(n.jsx)(w,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.817c943b.chunk.js.map